[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In marine science, ichthyology, branch of zoology closely related to marine biology and oceanography, is the study of what?", "correct_answer": "Fish", "incorrect_answers": ["Microscopic marine life", "Marine mammals", "Marine plant life"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which is a successful Australian comedy film?", "correct_answer": "Alvin Purple", "incorrect_answers": ["Sea of Purple", "Purple Kangas", "Purple Amethyst"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Bao yu, a prized ingredient used in many Chinese dishes, is what type of sea food?", "correct_answer": "Sea snail", "incorrect_answers": ["Sea cucumber", "Seaweed", "Shrimp"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "When threatened, this fish, also known as balloonfish, increases in size by swallowing water or air.", "correct_answer": "Porcupinefish", "incorrect_answers": ["Bowfin", "Bichir", "Oar fish"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In which US city did Einstein live out his last years?", "correct_answer": "Princeton, New Jersey", "incorrect_answers": ["Cambridge, Massachusetts", "New Haven, Connecticut", "Boca Raton, Florida"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "He confesses to the General that there was something disturbing about personally executing Gassim. It was not the blood  . . . \u201cNo, not that, something else; I enjoyed it.\u201d Name the movie.", "correct_answer": "Lawrence of Arabia", "incorrect_answers": ["Sparticus", "The Dirty Dozen", "Bridge Over the River Kwai"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "BVD is a brand of mens underwear, commonly referred to as BVDs. What does BVD stand for?", "correct_answer": "Bradley, Voorhees and Day", "incorrect_answers": ["Black, Victor and Dorn", "Basic Value Dressing", "Big Value Designer"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What type of food is the popular Swedish dish called Surstromming?", "correct_answer": "Fish", "incorrect_answers": ["Salad", "Soup", "Dessert"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What bat species is considered the largest in the world?", "correct_answer": "Golden-capped fruit bat", "incorrect_answers": ["Livingstone\u2019s Fruit Bat", "Fijian Monkey-faced Bat", "Hammer-headed bat"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these parts of the Sun is the warmest?", "correct_answer": "Corona", "incorrect_answers": ["Photosphere", "Prominences", "Chromosphere"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "During The Restoration period blond hair became a symbol of this.", "correct_answer": "Prostitution", "incorrect_answers": ["Stupidity", "High class", "Intelligence"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the diameter of planet Mercury?", "correct_answer": "4,878 km / 3 031 miles", "incorrect_answers": ["10,787 km / 6,702 miles", "983 km / 610 miles", "3,576 km / 2 222 miles"]}]